Guide to the Division of Continuing Education records, 1937-2003 RG0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Continuing education files, 1964-2003; RG0016 Series 3; 19.25 Linear Feet; 19.25 Linear feet
  - CHRON, 07/1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - CHRON, 08/1994 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - CHRON, 09/1994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - CHRON, 10/1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - CHRON, 11/1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - CHRON, 12/1994 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - CHRON, Distance Education for GWU, 1992 -1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Division of Continuing Education (DCE)-Annual Report, 1990 -1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - DCE-Annual Report with attachments, 1990 -1991 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - DCE-Annual Report, 1991 -1992 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - DCE-Aramian Analysis, 11/1992 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - DCE-CHRON/Misc., 1989 -1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - DCE-Income report, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Graduate School of Education & Human Development Report to National Council for the Accreditation of Teacher Education, Vol. I, 04/22/1995 --04/26/1995 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Graduate School of Education & Human Development Report to National Council for the Accreditation of Teacher Education, Vol. II, 04/22/1995 --04/26/1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Education Policy Studies -various booklets, 1995 -2001 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous papers, correspondence, invitations, 1992 -1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - National University Continuing Education Association (NUCEA)-National Conference in Boston, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NUCEA-policies, 1988 -1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Reorganization charts, 1991 -1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - School of Education & Human Development (SEHD)-Alumni Council meeting, 09/30/1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Schedule of Classes & brochures-Continuing & Graduate programs, 1986 -1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Speeches by Abbie O. Smith, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Training Officers Conference (TOC)-Annual Institute, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Negatives, 1970 ca. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Negatives, 1970 ca. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Photos, 1970 ca. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Photos & negatives, 1974 ca. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Photos, 1975 ca. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Photos, 09/1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Photos, 09/1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Photos-Black and white, 1970 ca. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Photos-College of General Studies (CGS), 1965 ca. --1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Also includes: newspaper & negatives
  - Photos & negatives-Continuing Education, 1970 ca. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Photos-Continuing Education (contains photos of President Lloyd Elliott), 1975 ca. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Photos & negatives-Humphrey's Hall, West Gate/West Park, Roosevelt H.S., 1970 ca. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Photos-L.A. Briefing, 05/1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Photos & Negatives-L.A. Reception, 07/18/1978 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Photos-Maryland State Police Headquarters at Pikesville, M.D. & Defense Mapping Agency Topographic Center, 1984 ca. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Photos & negatives, 1970 ca. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Photos & negatives, 09/1983 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Photos & negatives by Bud Paul, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Photos & negatives (including Ruth Osborn, President Elliott, Gerry & Bob Holland), 1978 ca. (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Photos-Opening of D.C. Metro, Continuing Education people, 1976 ca. (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Photos-Phi Delta Kappa Graduates, 1998 ca. (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Photos-Registration at Largo H.S., 05/1978 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Photos-Registration at Pentagon Concourse, 05/03/1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Photos-Tidewater Sun, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Photos-Women's Committee Lunch, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Telecommunications-Telecommunication History, 1987-1991; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications-Merger, 2002-2004; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications-Directories, 1973-1995; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications-AlumNET Publications, 1973-1994; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Telecommunications-Program Review, 1997-2001; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Telecommunications-Review/Strategic Plan - Final Documents, 1997-1999; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Telecommunications-TCOM Advisory Board, 2001-2002; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Telecommunications-Portugal Nova Forum, 2001; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications-Contract-FCC, 2001-2003; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications-Certificate, 2001-2003; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications-Adjuncts, 2000-2002; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Telecommunications-Team Engineering Courses, 2001; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Distinguished alumni awards, 1937-1999; RG0016 Series 4; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of biographical files and photographs of distinguished alumni award winners and those nominated. The materials range in date from 1937-1999.
  - Biographical information on Distinguished Alumni Award recipients, 1938 -1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lists of Distinguished Alumni Award Winners, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Draft of book Distinguished Alumni Achievement Award Winners, 1937 -1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Prominent Alumni, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Board of Trustees & Officers of Administration, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adams, Eva, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen, Teddy, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Photo or negative in the file
  - Alpher, Ralph, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Amram, David, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arundell, Charles, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Axelrod, Julius, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Auerbach, Red, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Baker, Edgar, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Barlow, Joel, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Barnes, Michael, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Barr, William, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Belen, Frederick, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bellows, Everett, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Benitez, Helena, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bennett, James, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bird, Frances, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Block, Karl, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bond, Lydia, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bradford, Harold, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Brady, Luther, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Brand, Vance, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Brennan, Nancy, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Briggs, W. Paul, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Brin, Carlos, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Brooks, Elmer, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Brown, Ann, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Brown, Mary, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Burns, Jacob, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Butler, George, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Cardinale, Anthony, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Carr, Wilbur, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Carrico, Harry, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Castell, Donald, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cisneros, Henry, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Cluff, Leighton, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Coblentz, Catherine, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Coe, Conway, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cohn, Meta, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Connelly, Mary, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cook, Donald, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Cooper, Irving, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Coughlin, Mildred, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Danzansky, Joseph, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Davidson, Robert, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Davis, Ewin, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Davis, Watson, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Davis, William, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Davison, Frederick, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - DeVita, Vincent, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Dewberry, Sidney, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Dowling, Harry, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Draper, Elizabeth, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Driver, William, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Dulles, Allen, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Enlows, Harold F., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Evans, Jessie Fant, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Feeney, Edward, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Fernandez, Emilio, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Fichandler, Zelda, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Finley, David, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Flemming, Arthur, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Fulbright, William, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Gabriel, Charles, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Gasch, Oliver, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Gibbs, Malcolm, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Gibson, Jonathon, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Girouard, Philias, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Gnehm, Edward "Skip", 1992 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Goddard, James, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Goodman, Julian, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Graubard, Stephen, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Green, Elsie, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Greene, Harold, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Green, Joyce, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Gregory, Frederick, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Gude, Gilbert, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Harbison, Earle, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Harmon, Robert, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Harris, Patricia Roberts, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Hastings, George, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Hawkes, Anna, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Haycock, Robert, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Haydon, Edith, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Herrick, Lucile, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Holly Sandra, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Hopkins, Nevil, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Hopping, Louis, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Hughes, Harry R., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Hughes, Joseph, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Hughes, Sarah, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Hunt, Thelma, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Inouye, Daniel, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Jacobs, Leon, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - James, L. Eldon, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - James, William S., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Jaworski, Leon, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Kayser, Elmer Louis, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kelly, Catherine, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Kennedy, David M., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Kirkham, Francis, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Korcheck, Stephen, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Kuller, Lewis, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Lambert, Sam, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Lazarus, Gerald, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Leemans, Alphonse (Tuffy), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Lerman, Elizabeth, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Lind, Ida, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - London, J. Phillip, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Longanecker, David, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Manatt, Charles, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Manos, Pete, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Margolis, Doris, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Margolis, Lawrence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Martin, Patrick, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Mason, Jimilu, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Mason, John Russell, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Mayo, Bernard, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - McConnell, Harden, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - McKenzie, Floretta, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - McPeak, Gen. Merrill, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Meaney, Thomas F., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Meyer, Edward, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Miles, Jeanne, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Mitchell, Edward F., 1990 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Mitchell, James, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Newman, Helen, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Nichols, Louis, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Nordlinger, Bernard, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Noyes, Theodore, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Nyrop, Donald, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Osborn, Ruth, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Page, Robert, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Patch, Lela, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Powell, Colin, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Proctor, James, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Proschan, Frank, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Reed, Charles, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Reichelderfer, Luther, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Reid, Mildred, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Rhee, Syngman, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Rhyne, Charles, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Richmond, Alfred, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Roe, Joseph, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Rogers, C.B., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Schoenfeld, H. Arthur, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Schoenfeld, Rudolph, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Schult, Veryl, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Shanahan, Eileen, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Shepard, Donald, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Shin, Nakyun, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Shirley, Dallas, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Shulman, Neil, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Smith, J. Clay, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Starr, Kenneth, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Strupp, Hans, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Thompson, Winifred, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Tolson, Clyde, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Tolson, Hillory, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Townsend, Marjorie, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Tracy, Stanley, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Van Vleck, William, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Vessey Jr., John, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Wallis, Richard, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Walsh, John, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Wedel, Cynthia, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Weddell, Alexander, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Weitzel, Frank, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - Wells, Elva, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Wetmore, Alexander, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Wheeler, Harold, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - White, Emilie, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - White, William, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Wilkinson, Ernest, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Wilkinson, Glen, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Willis, Benjamin, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Wilson, Elizabeth, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Wilson, John J., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Wilson, John T., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Wright, James, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Wright, Joseph, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Yates, Frank, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Unidentified photo and negatives, undated (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Abbot, Charles, undated (Box 1, Folder 191)
    Non-DAA winner
  - Adams, Dr. Joseph, undated (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Ahmed, Aftab, undated (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Anderson, Myron, undated (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Barrett, Jesse, undated (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Baughman, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Baum, Carter, undated (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Belcher, Carl, undated (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Beveridge, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Black, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Broome, Edwin, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brown, Vernon, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Broyhill, Joel, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Brigham, Gertrude, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Brewster, Daniel, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Burnett, Arden, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Byrd, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Carlson, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Calver, George W., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Calvert, Joan P., undated (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - Camalier, C. Willard, undated (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - Carr, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - Coe, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 213)
  - Considine, Bob, undated (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - Crain, Darrell C., undated (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - Cunningham, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - Dallwig, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - Frankel, Diane, undated (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - Kennedy, Jacqueline Bouvier, undated (Box 1, Folder 219)